Guide to the Mexican Movie Stills and Lobby Cards, 1937-1977 M1080
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
Mexican Movie Stills and Lobby Cards
1937-1977
M1080
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
10.5 Linear feet (19 flat boxes)
2,226 photographs from 280 movies, each title has 8 original lobby cards, unless noted by asterik.
Agrasanchez Film Archives
Collection Scope and Content Summary
There are two series: Series I consists of material arranged alphabetically by title, from 1937 to 1963. Series II consists of material arranged alphabetically by title, from 1963 to 1977.
Provenance
Agrasanchez Film Archive
Acquisition Information
Purchased, 1999
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Motion pictures--Mexico--History.; Photographs.; Photoprints.; Stills (Motion pictures)
- Series 1: 1937-1963
  - ABISMOS DE PASION (1953) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AHORA SOYRICO (1952) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - LOS AMORES DE MARIETA (1963) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AY AMOR, COMO ME HAS PUESTO (1950) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ANGELITOS NEGROS (1948) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ASESINOS, S.A. (1956) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ASI ES MI TIERRA (1937) *6 cards (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A.T.M. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - LA AUSENTE (1951) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - BAJO EL CIELO DE SONORA (1947) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - BAJO EL MANTO BE LA NOCHE (1962) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - EL BARCHANTE NEGUIB (1945) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - LA BELLAOTERO (1954) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - LA BESTIA MAGNIFICA (1952) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - BODAS DE FUEGO (1949) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - BORRASCA EN LAS ALMAS (1953) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - EL BRUTO (1952) *7 cards (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - CABARET TRAGICO (1957) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - CAFECOLON (1958) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - LA CALLE DE LOS AMORES (1953) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - CAMELIA (1953) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - CARCEL DE MUJERES (1951) *7 cards (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - CASA DEMUNECAS (1953) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - CASA DE PERDICION (1954) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - EL CASO DE LA MUJER ASESINADITA (1954) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - CON QUIEN ANDAN NUESTRAS HIJAS? (1955) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - COQUETA (1949) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - CUANDO LOS PADRES SE QUEDAN SOLOS (1948) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - CUANDO VUELVAS A MI (1953) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - LA CULPA DELOS HOMBRES (1954) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - EL CHARRO DEL ARRABAL (1948) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - EL CHARRO INMORTAL (1955) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - DANCING; SALON DE BAILE (1951) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - DESEADA (1950) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - DIOS LOS CRIA (1953) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - DONA MARIQUITA DE MI CORAZON (1952) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - DOS MUNDOS Y UN AMOR (1954) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - DOS PESOS DEJADA (1949) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - DOS TIPOS DE CUIDADO (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - LA DUDA (1953) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - ELLA Y YO (1951) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - ENTRE ABOGADOS TE VEAS (1950) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - ESTAFA DE AMOR (1954) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - ESTOY TAN ENAMORADA (1954) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - EUGENIA GRANDET (1952) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - UN EXTRANO ENLA ESCALERA (1954) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - FANTASIA RANCHERA (1943) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - FELICIDAD (1956) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - LOS FERNÁNDEZ DE PERALVILLO (1953) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - FURIA ROJA (1950) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - UNA GALLEGA EN LA HABANA (1955) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - EL GRAN AUTOR (1953) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - LA HIJA DE LA OTRA (1950) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - HIJAS CASADERAS (1954) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - EL HOMBRE QUE QUISO SER POBRE (1955) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - EL IMPOSTOR (1956) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - LA ISLA DE LAS MUJERES (1952) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - LAS ISLAS MARIAS (1950) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - LA LADRONA (1953) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - LAGRIMAS ROBADAS (1953) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - LO QUE SE OCULTO AL MUNDO (1951) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - LLEVAME EN TUS BRAZOS (1953) *7cards (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - LLUVIA ROJA (1949) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - MALDITAS SEAN LAS MUJERES (1936) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - MARIBEL Y LA EXTRANA FAMILIA (1960) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - EL MARIDO DE MI NOVIA (1950) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - MAS FUERTE QUE EL AMOR (1953) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - EL MENSAJE DE LA MUERTE (1952) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - MI CAMPEON (1951) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - MIERCOLES DE CENIZA (1958) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - MIRADAS QUE MA TAN (1953) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - EL MISTERIO DEL CARRO EXPRESS. (1952) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - MORENA DE MI COPLA (1945) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - MORIR DE PIE (1955) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - LA MUJER AJENA (1954) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - UNA MUJER EN LA CALLE (1954) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - MUJERES DEL PARAISO (1953) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - MULATA (1953) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - NAZARIN (1958) (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - EL NINO Y LA NIEBLA (1953) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - NOCHES DE RONDA (1942) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - NO DESEARAS LA MUJER DE TU HIJO (1949) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - EL NORTEN0 (1943) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - NUNCA DEBIERON AMARSE (1951) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - NUNCA ES TARDE PARA AMAR (1952) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - LA OVEJA NEGRA (1949) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - LA PASION DESNUDA (1952) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - EL PECADO DE SER MUJER (1954) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - PECADO MORTAL (1954) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - LA PERLA (1945) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - EL PENON DE LAS ANIMAS (1942) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - PEPE EL TORO (1952) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - LA PERVERSA (1953) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - PINTAME ANGELITOS BLANCOS (1954) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - EL PLAGIARIO (1953) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - POMPEYO EL CONQUISTADOR (1951) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - EL PORTICO DE LA GLORIA (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - LA POSESION (1949) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - PRISION DE SUENOS (1948) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - EL PUERTO DE LOS 7 VICIOS (1951) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - QUÉ TE HA DADO ESA MUJER? (1951) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - DEL RANCHO A LA CAPITAL (1941) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - RECIEN CASADOS, NO MOLESTAR (1950) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - LA RED (1953) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - LA REINA DEL MAMBO (1950) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - EL RENCOR BE LA TIERRA (1949) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - RETO A LA VIBA (1953) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - REVENTA BE ESCLA VAS (1953) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - EL RIO YLA MUERTE (1954) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - ROSTROS OLVIDADOS (1952) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - EL RUISENOR DEL BARRIO (1951) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - SANDRA LA MUJER BE FUEGO (1952) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - SECRETO ENTRE MUJERES (1948) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - EL SEMINARISTA (1949) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - SENBA PROHIBIDA (1959) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - SENSUALIDAD (1950) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - SENORA AMA (1954) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - SI ADELITA SE FUERA CON OTRO (1948) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - EL SIGNO BE LA MUERTE (1939) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - SI MI VIDA (1952) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - SINDICATO DE TELEMIRONES (1953) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - LA SOBRINA DEL SENOR CURA (1954) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - SOLAMENTE UNA VEZ (1953) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - SOMBRA VERDE (1954) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - SOR ALEGRIA (1952) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - LA SOSPECHOSA (1954) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - SOY UN GOLFO (1955) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - SUSANA (1950) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - TALPA (1955) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - EL TREN EXPRESO (1953) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - LA ULTIMA NOCHE (1948) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - EL VENDEDOR BE MUNECAS (1954) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - LA VENGANZA DEL CHARRO NEGRO (1941) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - LA VIDA TIENE TRES DIAS (1954) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - LOS VIEJOS SOMOS ASI (1948) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - EL VIOLETERO (1960) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - LA VISITA QUE NO TOCO EL TIEMBRE (1954) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - EL VIZCONDE BE MONTECRIS TO (1954) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Y DIOS LA LLAMO TIERRA (1960) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - YO MATE A ROSITA ALVIREZ (1946) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - YO SOY MUY MACHO (1953) (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Series II: 1963-1972
  - A GENTE VIAJERO, EL (1974) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - AMARGURA DEMIRAZA, LA (1972) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - ANONIMO MORTAL (1970) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - APARIENCIAS ENGANAN, LAS (1977) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ARDIENTE DESEO, EL (1970) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - ARTE DE ENGARAR, EL (1970) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - AVENTURAS DE UN CABALLO BLANCO (1973) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - BANG BANG, AL HOYO (1970) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - BESTIAS DEL TERROR, LAS (1972~) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - CAMINO, UN (1972) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - CANCION DEL ALMA (1963) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - CAPULINA CONTRA LOS MONSTRUOS (1973) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - CARGANDO CON EL MUERTO (1964,) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - CASA FLORA (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - CAPTURA DE GABINO BARRERA, LA (1967) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - CINICO, EL (1968) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - CORROMPIDOS, LOS (1970) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - CRISTO 70 (1969) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CUNA DE VALIENTES (1971) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CUANDO QUIERO LLORAR NO LLORO (1972) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CHANOC CONTRA EL TIGRE YEL VAMPIRO (1971) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - CHICO RAMOS (1970) *7cards (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - DE SANGRE CHICANA (1973) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - DEBIERON AHORCARLOS ANTES (1973) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - DESCONOCIDO, EL (1973) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - DOMINGO SALVAJE (1966) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - DON QUIJOTE CABALGA DE NUEVO (1972) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - DONA MACABRA (1971) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - DORADO DE PANCHO VILLA, UN (1966) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - DOS CABALLEROS DE ESPADA (1963) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - DOS HERMANOS, LOS (1970) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - ENCUENTRO DE UN HOMBRE SOLO, EL (1973,) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - EVA Y DARIO (1972) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - EXTRANO AMOR, UN (1974) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - FANTASTICO MUNDO DE LOS HIPPIES, EL (1969) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - FE, ESPERANZA Y CARIDAD (1972) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - FIDELIDAD, LA (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - FLORMARCHITA (1968) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - FUERZA INUTIL, LA (1970) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - FUERZAS VIVAS, LAS (1975) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - FUGA EN LA NOCHE (1972) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - FURIAS BAJO EL CIELO (1970) *6 cards (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - GIGANTES PLANETARIOS (1966) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - GITANO (1972) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - HEMBRA MALDITA, LA (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - HIJO DE ANGELA MARIA, EL (1974) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - INDOMABLES, LOS (1971) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - IMPONENTE, EL (1972) *6 cards (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - INSACIABLE, LA (1970) *7 cards (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - INVESTIGADOR CAPULINA, EL (1973) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - ISLA DE LOS HOMBRES SOLOS, LA (1973) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - JESUS EL NINO DIOS (1969) *8 cards (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - JUEZ DE LA SOGA, EL (1972) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - JUICIO BE LOS HIJOS, EL (1970) *7 cards (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - JUVENTUD DESNUDA (1970) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - KALIMAN EL INCREIBLE (1970) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - LABERINTO DE PASIONES (1970) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - LAGRIMAS DE MI BARRIO (1972) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - LIBERTAD PARA LA JUVENTUD (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - LIO BE FALDAS (1969) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - LUCHA CON LA PANTERA, LA (1974) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - LLANTO BE LA TORTUGA, EL (1974) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - LLANTO, RISAS Y KNOCK OUT (1973) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - MAFIA AMARILLA, LA (1975) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - MANOS TORPES (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - MANSION DE LA LOCURA, LA (1971) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - MANUEL SALDI VAR, EL TEXANO (1970) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - MARCHANTA, LA (1973) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - MARIANA (1967) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - MAS ALLA DE LA VIOLENCIA (1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - MA TERNIDAD SIN HOMBRES (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - ME CAI DE LA NUBE (1974) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - MEMORIAS BE MI GENERAL, LAS (1960) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - MESES Y LOS DIAS, LOS (1971) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - MEXICO DE NOCHE (1974) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - MI VENTURA EN PUERTO RICO (1974) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - MI NINO TIZOC (1971) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - MUJER DEL DIABLO, LA (1972) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - NINO (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - NO OYES LADRAR LOS PERROS? (1974) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - NOCHE VIOLENTA, LA (1969) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - ORGANIZACION CRIMINAL (1968) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - OTRA VIRGINIDAD, LA (1974) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - PANICO (1970) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - PARAISO (1969) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - PECADO DE ADAN Y EVA, EL (1967) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - PECADORAS, LAS (1967) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - PELUQUERO DE SENORAS (1971) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - PEOR QUE LOS BUITRES (1973) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - PEQUENO ROBIN HOOD, EL (1973) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - PERROS DE DIOS, LOS (1973) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - PLANETA DE LAS MUJERES INVASORAS (1965) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - PRESAGIO (1974) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - PRIMER AMOR, EL (1 9 72) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - PRIMER PASO DE LA MUJER, EL (1971) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - PRINCIPIO, EL (1972) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - PROBLEMAS DE MAMA, LOS (1968) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - QUIEN MATO AL ABUELO? (1971) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - RAPAZ, EL (1967) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - RAPINA (1973) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - RECOGIDA, LA (1972) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - RINCON DE LAS VIRGENES, EL (1972) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - ROBINSON CRUSOE (1968) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - ROSA BLANCA (1961) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - SANGRE ENEMIGA, LA (1969) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - SAN SIMON BE LOS MAGUEYES (1972) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - SANTO OFICIO, EL (1973) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - SANTO VS LOS CAZADORES BE CABEZAS (1969) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - SANTO Y BLUE DEMON VS DRACULA Y EL HOMBRE LOBO (1972) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - SANTO Y BLUE DEMON VS DR. FRANKESTEIN (1974) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - SATANAS DE TODOS LOS HORRORES (1972) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - SENOR DE OSANTO, EL (1972) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - SIETE EVAS PARA ADAN (1969) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - SIETE MUERTES PARA EL TEXANO (1970) *7 cards (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - SIGUIENDO PISTAS (1959) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - SIMPLEMENTE MARIA (1970) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - SONRISA DE MAMA, LA (1972) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - SUPERZAN EL INVENCIBLE (1971) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - SUPERZAN Y EL NINO DEL ESPACIO (1972) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - TEJEDOR DE MILAGROS, EL (1961) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - TESORO DE MORGAN, EL (1974) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - TIVOLI (1974) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - TRINQUETERO, EL (1974) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - TU, YO, NOSOTROS (1970) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - VALENTE QUINTERO (1972,) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - VAMPIRO Y EL SEXO, EL (1968) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 24 HORAS DE PLACER (1968) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - VERANO ARDIENTE (1970) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - VEDADERA VOCACION DE MAGDALENA, LA (1971) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - VICTORIA (1971) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - VIDA INUTIL DE PITO PEREZ, LA (1969) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - VIDITA NEGRA (1971) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - VIRGENES LOCAS, LAS (1970) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - VIVA MEXICO Y SUS CORRIDOS (1982) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - YA SOMOS HOMBRES (1970) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - YANCO (1966) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - YESENIA (1971) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - YO AMO, TUA MAS, NOSOTROS... (1974) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - YO FUI VIOLADA (1977) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - ZINDY EL NINO DE LOS PANTANOS (1972) (Box 3, Folder 34)